Guide to the William Lockhart Clayton papers, 1897-1998 MS 007
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
William Lockhart Clayton papers
1897-1998, Bulk dates 1934-1964
1934-1964
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Clayton, William Lockhart, 1880-1966
MS 007
50 Linear Feet 102 boxes, 2 map drawers
Original personal material and photocopied professional materials relating to economist and foreign policy expert Will Clayton and family, dating from 1897-1998. In addition to serving the U.S. government in a number of capacities, Clayton was in cotton business, and a co-founder of Anderson, Clayton and Company, based in Houston, Texas.
Biographical Note
William Lockhart Clayton was born in Tupelo, Mississippi on February 7th, 1880. In August 1902 he was married to Susan Vaughan. He was a co-founder of Anderson, Clayton and Company, based in Houston, Texas. In 1918 Clayton was a member of the Committee on Cotton Distribution with the War Industries Board. From 1940 to 1942 he was the Vice President of the Export-Import Bank.
His career in government service began in 1942 with his appointment as Assistant Secretary of Commerce, followed by appointments as Administrator of the Surplus War Property Administration (1944), Assistant Secretary of State (1944-1945), Undersecretary of State for Economic Affairs (1945-1947), and as head of the U.S. delegation at the United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment, which took place in Havana, Cuba, in 1947.
Clayton also served in the following capacities: Alternate Governor, World Bank (1946-1949), Vice President, Atlantic Union Committee (1949-1961), member on the National Security Training Commission (1951-1954), Chairman, National Committee on Campaign Contributions and Expenditures (1960), member on the Board of Governors of the Atlantic Institute (1960), and as co-Chairman of the U.S. Citizens Commission on NATO (1961).
In the 1950s Clayton authored a number of books primarily dealing with economics and their political ramifications. These included "We Must Trade Sovereignty For Freedom" (1950), "The Road To Peace" (1955), "What Price Oil?" (1958), and "We Are Losing The Cold War" (1958).
William L. Clayton died on February 9th, 1966, in Houston, Texas.
Scope and Contents
The Clayton collection, covering the years 1897 to 1966, consists of ninety-nine boxes of originals and photocopies of business and personal correspondence, speeches, reports, photographs, memorabilia, and some oversize material such as certificates of appointment, which document the personal and professional life of Will Clayton and to a lesser degree, the Clayton family. Original materials in the collection relate to Clayton's personal and family life, including family correspondence and photographs, and oral histories by Clayton's daughter, Ellen Clayton Garwood, relating to her father's legacy. This original material is located in Series VI through XI.
The bulk of the collection, in Series II (boxes 2-86), is comprised of photocopies of Clayton correspondence gleaned from numerous other institutions. The photocopied materials in this series were identified, ordered, and purchased by Frederick J. Dobney, Editor, Public Papers of William L. Clayton, Rice University, in the year 1967. The resulting compilation of materials was in 1971 as "Selected Papers of Will Clayton," published by Johns Hopkins University, edited by Dobney. While these materials are not original, they are convenient as a Clayton research collection, especially when used in coordination with the cardfile index which provides author / recipient name access to the chronologically arranged correspondence.
Access Restrictions
Material is open for research; permission to photocopy must be obtained from Director, WRC.
Acquisition Information
Original materials were donated by Ellen Clayton Garwood, daughter of Will Clayton.
The photocopied materials in the collection were identified, ordered, and purchased by Frederick J. Dobney, Editor, Public Papers of William L. Clayton, Rice University, in the year 1967. The resulting compilation of materials was in 1971 as "Selected Papers of Will Clayton," published by Johns Hopkins University, edited by Dobney.
Related Material
Other significant William L. Clayton papers are at the National Archives, the Truman Library, and the Hoover Institution, Stanford University. Lesser holdings are at the Cossitt-Goodwyn branch of the Memphis/Shelby County Public Library. Some time in the early 1980s a small group of papers went to the Houston Metropolitan Center of the Houston Public Library when Anderson, Clayton and Co. was acquired by Quaker Oats.
Cardfile Index to Clayton Papers
The bulk of the Clayton materials is comprised of the correspondence and notes in Series II: Papers, which is arranged chronologically and has only a few subject files at the end of the series. To locate specific author/senders, recipients, dates, sources of photocopies in Series II (boxes 2-85), use the 11 box cardfile index as described here.
DATE: Cardfile boxes 1-3. Box 1: no date and 1921-45; Box 2: 1946-June 1959; Box 3:July 1959-1967. Listed chronologically by year, with name of sender at top, name of recipient under sender's name, length of item, brief summary of contents, and at bottom, acronym or abbreviation for repository which owns the original.
AUTHOR / SENDER: Cardfile boxes 4-6. Box 4: A-Clayton (1949); Box 5: Clayton (1950-1966); Box 3: D-Z. These cards give the name of the author / sender; date of correspondence or item; brief summary of contents; and at the bottom, acronym or abbreviation for repository which owns the original.
RECIPIENT: Cardfile boxes 7-9. Box 7: Clayton; Box 8: A-K; Box 9: L-Z. Format of card info is same as for AUTHOR / SENDER cards.
SOURCES OF PHOTOCOPIES: Cardfile boxes 10-11. Repositories listed alphabetically by acronyms or abbreviations, such as:
ACCO: Anderson Clayton Co.
FL: Fondren Library (Rice University)
Nat. Arch.: National Archives
Univ. of Cal.: University of California, Bancroft Library
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center and requires 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Index Terms
Subjects
Statesmen -- United States; Economic assistance, American; Cotton; Politics and government
Document Types
notes; diaries; oral histories (document genres); photographs; corrrespondence
Places
United States
Subjects (Persons)
Garwood, Ellen, 1903-; Garwood, St. John; Clayton, Susan Vaughan; Clayton, Anne Burdine; Clayton family
Subjects (Corporations)
Anderson, Clayton & Co.
- Series I: Dobney Project Correspondence, 1967, 250425; 1 Linear Feet
  - Correspondence with libraries related to Dobney project of collecting photocopies of Will Clayton papers in other repositories. Completed survey formsand response letters from various libraries document their Clayton holdings and the process of acquiring photocopies of them., 250426 (Box 1)
- Series II: Public Papers, 1926-1967, 250304; 86 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This, the largest of the series in this collection, is comprised of photocopies of letters to and from Will Clayton in his official capacities during the years 1926-1967.
  There are no original materials in this series; all materials are from repositories other than Rice.
  Items are filed in two groups: first, chronologically, with one item per folder, each with a citation for the holding repository. The second group is alphabetical by subject or correspondent, with as many clippings as pieces of correspondence.
  Use cardfile index to access these materials by sender / author name or by recipient name. Ask WRC staff for assistance.
  - Prior to 1924; 1924, 1926, 250424 (Box 2)
  - 1927-1931, 250423 (Box 3)
  - 1932-1933, 250422 (Box 4)
  - Jan.-June, 1934, 250421 (Box 5)
  - June-Nov., 1934, 250420 (Box 6)
  - Nov.-Dec., 1934; 1935, 250419 (Box 7)
  - 1936-1937; Jan.-May,1938, 250418 (Box 8)
  - May-Dec., 1938; Jan.-Aug., 1939, 250417 (Box 9)
  - Sept.-Dec., 1939; Jan.-Aug., 1940, 250416 (Box 10)
  - Aug.-Dec., 1940, 250415 (Box 11)
  - Jan.-June, 1941, 250414 (Box 12)
  - June-Dec., 1941; Jan.-Apr., 1942, 250413 (Box 13)
  - Apr.-Dec., 1942, 250412 (Box 14)
  - Jan.-May, 1943, 250411 (Box 15)
  - May-Dec., 1943, 250410 (Box 16)
  - Jan.-May, 1944, 250409 (Box 17)
  - June-Aug., 1944, 250408 (Box 18)
  - Sept.-Oct., 1944, 250407 (Box 19)
  - Nov.-Dec., 1944, 250406 (Box 20)
  - Jan.-Apr., 1945, 250405 (Box 21)
  - May-June, 1945, 250404 (Box 22)
  - June-July, 1945, 250403 (Box 23)
  - Aug.-Sept., 1945, 250402 (Box 24)
  - Oct. 1945, 250401 (Box 25)
  - Nov.-Dec., 1945, 250400 (Box 26)
  - Jan.-Apr., 1946, 250399 (Box 27)
  - May-Aug., 1946, 250398 (Box 28)
  - Sept.-Dec., 1946; Jan.-Feb, 1947, 250397 (Box 29)
  - March-Sept., 1947, 250396 (Box 30)
  - Oct.-Nov., 1947, 250395 (Box 31)
  - Dec. 1947; Jan.-Apr., 1948, 250394 (Box 32)
  - May-Nov., 1948, 250393 (Box 33)
  - Nov.-Dec., 1948; Jan., 1949, 250392 (Box 34)
  - Jan.-March, 1949, 250391 (Box 35)
  - Apr.-July, 1949, 250390 (Box 36)
  - Aug.-Nov., 1949, 250389 (Box 37)
  - Dec., 1949; Jan., 1950, 250388 (Box 38)
  - Feb.-May, 1950, 250387 (Box 39)
  - June-Nov., 1950, 250386 (Box 40)
  - Dec., 1950; Jan.-Feb., 1951, 250385 (Box 41)
  - Mar.-Dec., 1951, 250384 (Box 42)
  - Jan.-Nov., 1952, 250383 (Box 43)
  - Dec., 1952; 1953, 250382 (Box 44)
  - 1954; Jan.-Feb., 1955, 250381 (Box 45)
  - March-Dec., 1955; Jan.-Apr., 1956, 250380 (Box 46)
  - May-Dec., 1956; 1957, 250379 (Box 47)
  - Jan.-June, 1958, 250378 (Box 48)
  - July-Aug., 1958, 250377 (Box 49)
  - Aug.-Sept., 1958, 250376 (Box 50)
  - Sept.-Dec., 1958, 250375 (Box 51)
  - Jan.-Feb., 1959, 250374 (Box 52)
  - March-Apr., 1959, 250373 (Box 53)
  - May-June, 1959, 250372 (Box 54)
  - July-Aug., 1959, 250371 (Box 55)
  - Aug.-Oct., 1959, 250370 (Box 56)
  - Oct.-Dec., 1959, 250369 (Box 57)
  - Jan.-March, 1960, 250368 (Box 58)
  - Apr.-May, 1960, 250367 (Box 59)
  - June-July, 1960, 250366 (Box 60)
  - Aug.-Sept., 1960, 250365 (Box 61)
  - Oct.-Nov., 1960, 250364 (Box 62)
  - Nov.-Dec., 1960; Jan.-Feb., 1961, 250363 (Box 63)
  - Feb.-March, 1961, 250362 (Box 64)
  - March-Apr., 1961, 250361 (Box 65)
  - Apr.-June, 1961, 250360 (Box 66)
  - July, 1961, 250359 (Box 67)
  - Aug.-Sept., 1961, 250358 (Box 68)
  - Sept.-Nov., 1961, 250357 (Box 69)
  - Nov.-Dec., 1961, 250356 (Box 70)
  - Jan.-Feb., 1962, 250355 (Box 71)
  - March-May, 1962, 250354 (Box 72)
  - June-Aug., 1962, 250353 (Box 73)
  - Sept.-Dec., 1962, 250352 (Box 74)
  - Jan.-Feb., 1963, 250351 (Box 75)
  - March-May, 1963, 250350 (Box 76)
  - June-Aug., 1963, 250349 (Box 77)
  - Sept.-Nov., 1963, 250348 (Box 78)
  - Dec., 1978; Jan., 1964, 250347 (Box 79)
  - Feb.-June, 1964, 250346 (Box 80)
  - July-Dec., 1964, 250345 (Box 81)
  - Jan.-Aug., 1965, 250344 (Box 82)
  - Sept.-Dec., 1965; 1966-67, Miscellaneous, 250343 (Box 83)
  - Photocopies of papers in Truman Library (unfoldered), 250342 (Box 84)
  - Photocopies of WLC papers in Truman library (unfoldered), 250341 (Box 85)
  - Photocopies of WLC papers in National Archives, Civil Archives, Diplomatic Branch, 1944-45, 250340 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Photocopies of WLC papers in FDR Library, Sherwood Collection, Harry Hopkins Papers, 1940-45, 250339 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Unsorted general professional correspondence, 1951-65, 250338 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Unsorted cotton related professional correspondence, 1961-63, 250337 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence sorted by correspondent, 1947-1959, 250336 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - A.A.A., 1933-34, 250335 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - A.A.A., 1934-35, 250334 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Agriculture, Cotton Crops, 1959, 250333 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, 1948-49, 250332 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Anderson, Clayton & Cia., 1958-59, 250331 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Anderson, Clayton & Cia., 1959-60, 250330 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Declaration, 1961, 250329 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Budget: Interest Rates, Barter, and Stockpiling, 1959, 250328 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Commission of Inquiry on national Policy in International Economic Relations, 1933-34, 250327 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Economic Development, 1949-51, 250326 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Congress, 1952, 250325 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Contributions, 1947-49, 250324 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Cotton Exchanges, 1950-51, 250323 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Crisis Committee, 1950-51, 250322 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Doughs, Hon. L.W., 1953-1966, 250321 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Economic Cooperation Administration, 1950-51, 250320 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Fletcher School of Law & Diplomacy, 1950-51, 250319 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - House and Senate, 1950-51, 250318 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Intergovernmental debts, 1933-34, 250317 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - International Economic Union, 1955, 250316 (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - International Trade: Common Market, 1958-59, 250315 (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - Japanese International Christian University, 1949-51, 250314 (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1950-51, 250313 (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - Politics: Coops, 1960, 250312 (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - Politics: State, 1958-59, 250311 (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - Resignation letters, A-L, 1947, 250310 (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - Senators & Congressmen, 1948-51, 250309 (Box 86, Folder 30)
  - Senators & Representatives, 1934-35, 250308 (Box 86, Folder 31)
  - Senators & Representatives, 1938-39, 250307 (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Susan V. Clayton Slum Clearance Foundation, 1949-52, 250306 (Box 86, Folder 33)
  - Tariffs, 1937-38, 250305 (Box 86, Folder 34)
- Series III: Microfilm and Audiotape Copies of Related Materials, 1945-64, n.d., 250298; 1 Linear Feet
  Microfilm and audiotape holdings related to Clayton; originals held in repositories other than Rice.
  - Truman library, 5 reels: Papers of WLC, Chron. file:; Alpha. file - World Trade Fdtn.; Papers of WLC, Papers of. E.C. Garwood, Official File, President's Personal File, Bill File., June 1, 1945-1964; 250303 (Box 87)
  - Library of Congress, 2 reels, no R.G. #, 250302 (Box 87)
  - Princeton Library, 1 reel, no R.G.#., 250301 (Box 87)
  - National Archives, 4 reels. Selected Documents Relating to WLC from the RFC, Commerce and Interior Records; (R.G. 234, 40, 48); untitled, R.G. 16, 83, 145, 250300 (Box 87)
  - Audiotape, 4 reels. Will Clayton, Columbia University Oral History. See transcript in Biographical Series., 250299 (Box 87)
- Series IV: Senate Hearing Investigating the Causes of the Decline of Cotton, 1936, 250295; 2 Linear Feet
  U.S. Government published transcripts of Senate hearings. Bound volumes are unfoldered and filed in numerical order by volume.
  - Hearing before the Committee on Agriculture and Forestry of the U.S. Senate... to Investigate the Causes of the Decline of Cotton Prices, vol. 1, 3-10, 250297 (Box 88)
  - Hearing before the Committee on Agriculture and Forestry of the U.S. Senate... to Investigate the Causes of the Decline of Cotton Prices vol. 11-19, 250296 (Box 89)
- Series V: Clippings, 1945-62, 250291; 3 folders, 0.5 linear inches
  - Newspaper clippings, 1945-62; 250294 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - French newspaper quotes on Clayton and Marshall Plan, 1947, 250293 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - London Times index to articles on Clayton, 1947; 250292 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Series VI: Personal and Family Correspondence, 1899-1964; 250197; 5 boxes, 2.5 linear ft.
  Arranged in two subseries: A: Original correspondence, and B: Photocopies of correspondence. Both arranged by correspondent and then by date.
  - Subseries A: Original correspondence, 250273
    - WLC/St. John Garwood, 1929-30; 250290 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - WLC/St. John Garwood, 1930-31; 250289 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - WLC/St. John Garwood, 1931-32; 250288 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - WLC/St. John Garwood, 1932-33; 250287 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - WLC/St. John Garwood, 1933-34; 250286 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - WLC/St. John Garwood, 1934-35; 250285 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - WLC/St. John Garwood, 1935-36; 250284 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - WLC/St. John Garwood, 1936-37; 250283 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - WLC/St. John Garwood, 1938-39; 250282 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - WLC/St. John Garwood, 1939-40; 250281 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Mixed personal family notes and correspondence, 1900-1930; 250280 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Mixed personal family correspondence, 1907-1963; 250279 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Clayton, Anne Burdine, notes, drawings, photographs, 1916; 250278 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Clayton, Ellen Burdine, matriculation, Bryn Mawr College, 1919; 250277 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Clayton, Ellen [Garwood], correspondence to and from parents, 1911-1964; 250276 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Clayton, Julia Scott, 1917, n.d.; 250275 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Clayton, Susan: essay, 1916; 250274 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Subseries B: Photocopied correspondence from repositories other then Rice, 250198
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Sept. 1899; 250272 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Oct. 1899; 250271 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Nov. 1899; 250270 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Dec. 1899; 250269 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Jan. 1900; 250268 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Feb. 1900; 250267 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, March, 1900; 250266 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, April, 1900; 250265 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, May, 1900; 250264 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, June, 1900; 250263 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, July, 1900; 250262 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, August, 1900; 250261 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Septemeber, 1900; 250260 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, October, 1900; 250259 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Nov., 1900; 250258 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Dec., 1900; 250257 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Jan., 1901; 250256 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Feb., 1901; 250255 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Mar., 1901; 250254 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Apr., 1901; 250253 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, May, 1901; 250252 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, June, 1901; 250251 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, July, 1901; 250250 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Aug., 1901; 250249 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Sept., 1901; 250248 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Oct., 1901; 250247 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Nov., 1901; 250246 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Dec., 1901; 250245 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Jan., 1902; 250244 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Feb., 1902; 250243 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Mar., 1902; 250242 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Apr., 1902; 250241 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, May, 1902; 250240 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, June, 1902; 250239 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, July, 1902; 250238 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (photocopies) W. L. Clayton to Sue Vaughan, Aug., 1902; 250237 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - W. L. Clayton correspondence (photocopies) to Hattye Vaughan, 1900; 250236 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, 1897; 250235 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, 1898; 250234 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, 1899; 250233 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, Jan., 1900; 250232 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, Feb.-June, 1900; 250231 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, July-Aug., 1900; 250230 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, Sept., 1900; 250229 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, Oct.-Dec., 1900; 250228 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, Jan.-March, 1901; 250227 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, April, 1901; 250226 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, May, 1901; 250225 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, June, 1901; 250224 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, July, 1901; 250223 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, Aug., 1901; 250222 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, Sept., 1901; 250221 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, Oct., 1901; 250220 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, Nov., 1901; 250219 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, Dec., 1901; 250218 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, Jan., 1902; 250217 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, Feb., 1902; 250216 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, Mar., 1902; 250215 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, Apr., 1902; 250214 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, May, 1902; 250213 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, June, 1902; 250212 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, July, 1902; 250211 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Sue Vaughan correspondence (photocopies) to W.L. Clayton, 1902, 1904; 250210 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Misc. correspondence (photocopies) to Sue Vaughan and W.L. Clayton, 1898-1904; 250209 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Personal family correspondence (photocopies), ca. 1895-1903; 250208 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Personal family correspondence (photocopies), 1917-19; 250207 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Personal family correspondence (photocopies), 1920-22; 250206 (Box 95, Folder 7)